During a Monday afternoon press conference on the campus of Delta State University,
it was announced the body of 21-year-old Demartravian Trey Reed of Grenada,
a freshman at DSU, was found hanging from a tree near the pickleball courts
not far from the campus cafeteria.
At this time, there's no evidence of foul play.
I refuse to believe that he believes that.
He's a cop in Mississippi.
I don't know how anything changes if we're all moving in fear, you know?
I mean, maybe in Mississippi he has to say that to keep up a guise,
to do the real work behind the scenes.
I want to believe that.
I do.
I want to believe that for Trey.
I want to believe that for his parents.
I want to believe that for the second individual who was found hanged in Mississippi just yesterday.